asknow.com 2016-04-22

# AskNow.com

**Effective Date: March 17, 2005**

Thank you for visiting the AskNow® website at www.asknow.com (hereinafter referred to as the "Website"). The Website is brought to you by Qwando, LLC, doing business as AskNow® ("AskNow®", "we" and "us"). AskNow® respects the privacy of your personally identifiable information. To better protect your privacy, we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices available to you concerning the way that we use the information collected online at this Website. You agree to this Privacy Policy in its entirety when you: 1) access or use the Website; 2) purchase products and/or services from us; and/or 3) agree to receive an e-mail message from us. 

This Privacy Policy will address the following: 

> What information this Website gathers/tracks about you.   
>  What this Website does with the information it gathers/tracks.   
>  With whom this Website shares the information it gathers/tracks.   
>  This Website's opt-out policy. 

If you are a resident of the State of California and would like to opt-out from the disclosure of your personal information to any third-party for direct marketing purposes, please e-mail us at [CustomerService@Asknow.com](mailto:CustomerService@Asknow.com)

**Information We Collect:**   
Our goal in collecting personal information from you is to provide you with a smooth and efficient experience while you are using the Website's services, and to keep you informed of opportunities available on those services. This allows us to provide services and features that are most likely to meet your needs, and to customize our service to facilitate your experience.   

We collect personally identifiable information that you provide to us when you when you contact us, register with, and/or purchase products or services via, the Website or our toll-free telephone number. The types of personally identifiable information we may collect at this Website, or via the telephone, during registration and when you make a purchase include: 

> Name;   
>  Gender;   
>  E-mail address;   
>  Billing address and zip code;   
>  Credit card information, including expiration date and verification code;   
>  Zodiac sign;   
>  Telephone number; and   
>  Date of birth. 

AskNow® may create internal reports on user demographics and traffic patterns for our use and for use by our advertisers and partners. AskNow® may include your personal information in our reports. This information allows our third-party advertisers to deliver, and our users to receive, content-specific information and advertisements. To the extent that customer credit card-specific information is collected by AskNow® , said information will be kept in confidence and will not be shared with any third parties (other than consumer credit agencies) without the customer's prior informed consent. Notwithstanding the foregoing, AskNow® and its affiliates reserve the right to share with third-parties the fact that they have credit card information on file for specific customers, but they will not share more than the last four digits of this credit card information with third-parties without the customer's prior informed consent. 

In addition, we use log files to track anonymous user information including, but not limited to, Internet Protocol ("IP") addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider ("ISP"), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks. This information is tracked in order to analyze trends, administer the Website, track users' movements in the aggregate and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. The information tracked via log files is not linked to personally identifiable information. 

_Cookies_ :   
The Website uses a "cookie" to assign a unique identifier to your computer. The cookies we use are persistent files that your web browser places on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests, to save your password so that you do not have to remember it each time that you visit our Website, if you so choose, and for other purposes. No personally identifiable information is gathered by the cookie.   

**Our Use and Disclosure of Your Information.**   
The personally identifiable information that you submit to AskNow® remains your property. However, by submitting that information to us you grant AskNow® the right to use that information for any legal purpose including, without limitation: a) effectuating a purchase from AskNow® that you make at the Website; b) marketing purposes, such as sharing your information with third-party advertisers; c) providing promotional offers to you by means of e-mail, text or sms advertising, direct mail marketing, pop-ups, pop-unders and/or online banner advertising; and d) for validation, suppression, content improvement and feedback purposes. You agree that AskNow® may contact you at any time with updates and/or any other information that we may deem appropriate for you to receive in connection with your continued use of the Website. We also use contact information from your registration data to send you information about AskNow® and to keep you informed of our other products and services, and/or those of our affiliates, that may be of interest to you. Your contact information is also used to reach you, when necessary, regarding issues concerning purchases made on the Website. If you wish to stop receiving future communications from us, please see the Opt-Out section below.   

Except as explicitly stated herein, we do not sell, rent or trade any personally identifiable information to third-parties. We may sell our user information and/or join together with other businesses to bring selected opportunities to our users. AskNow® is able to offer our products and/or services to you, in part, based on your willingness to be reached by our third-party advertisers. By allowing us to make the information you supply available to these third-parties, you will receive free information on products and services that may be of interest to you. This information may also be shared with advertisers on an aggregate basis. In addition, you agree that such act constitutes a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application for purposes of the Amended Telemarketing Sales Rule, 16 C.F.R. § 310, et seq. (the "ATSR"). Notwithstanding that your telephone number may be listed on the Federal Trade Commission's Do-Not-Call List, AskNow® retains the right to contact you via telemarketing in accordance with the ATSR. Moreover, by registering with, or requesting information from, a third-party advertiser at or through the Website, such action shall constitute a purchase, an inquiry and/or an application with the respective third-party advertiser for purposes of the ATSR and you may be contacted via e-mail, direct mail and/or telemarketing by such third-party advertiser in accordance with the ATSR. 

We may be required to disclose personal information in some instances, such as: 1) when required by law wherein we have a good faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, and/or subpoena; 2) in the event that AskNow® is sold or acquired; or 3) in the event that we believe that the Website is being, or has been, used in violation of our terms and conditions or to commit unlawful acts. You hereby consent to the disclosure of any record or communication to any third-party when AskNow®, in its sole discretion, determines the disclosure to be appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your email address with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the provisions of the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time-to-time. 

**Third Party Links.**   
This Website may contain links to other third-party owned and/or operated websites. AskNow® is not responsible for any content, terms and conditions, or the privacy policies of such websites. The entities that advertise and/or place banner ads at the Website including, but not limited to, third-party advertisers, are independent third-parties and are not affiliated with AskNow®. We encourage you to review the policies of these sites.   

**Minors.**   
Persons under the age of 18 ("minors") are not eligible to register for, use and/or purchase the services and/or products featured on the Website. AskNow does not knowingly collect information from minors. No information should be submitted to, or posted at, this Website by individuals under 18 years of age. We encourage parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.   

**Security.**   
All collected information is stored in a technically and physically secure environment. Access to collected information is not available to the public and is strictly limited. Our employees are dedicated to ensuring the security and privacy of all AskNow® user information. To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy and ensure the correct use of information, we use appropriate industry standard procedures to safeguard the confidentiality of your personal information, such as firewall, encryption, token authentication, application proxies, monitoring technology, and adaptive analysis of network traffic to track abuse of our network and its data.   

In addition, AskNow® has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of personal information under our control. We employ Secure Socket Layer Software ("SSL") to protect certain financial information and associated data, and to secure any transactions. SSL encrypts information, including credit card numbers, as it is transmitted over the Internet. 

Please be advised that, although we take every reasonable technological precaution available to protect your data, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. 

**Opt-Out Procedure.**   
If you decide you would like to cancel your registration for an AskNow® product or service, you may do so by either clicking on the unsubscribe link located at the bottom of any e-mail received from AskNow® and following the instructions to unsubscribe, or by sending an e-mail with the subject "unsubscribe" to [CustomerService@Asknow.com](mailto:CustomerService@Asknow.com). Please specify in your e-mail from which AskNow® product or service you wish to unsubscribe. To unsubscribe from a third-party service, you must contact that third-party directly.   

**Changes to the Privacy Policy & Notification of Changes:**   
AskNow® reserves the right to change or update this Privacy Policy at any time by posting a notice at the Website that we are changing our Privacy Policy. If the manner in which we use personally identifiable information changes, we will notify users by posting the changes on this Website. Any and all changes to our Privacy Policy are effective immediately upon posting. The user's continued use of the Website, AskNow ® products and/or services, and/or continued receipt of AskNow® e-mails constitutes an affirmative acknowledgement and acceptance by the user to the terms of the modified Privacy Policy.   

**Contact Us.**   
If you have any questions about our Privacy Policy or would like more information on our privacy practices, please contact us via e-mail at [CustomerService@Asknow.com](mailto:CustomerService@Asknow.com), or by calling [1-800-660-1922](tel:1-800-660-1922), or by writing to:   
3665 East Bay Dr.   
Suite 204 E   
Largo FL 33771-1965
